A Guide to the Norfolk (Va.) Building Inspection Office Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1898-1980
Library of Virginia
- Office Building [Conversion from Service Station] - Permit Number: 65525, Address: 2216 Hampton Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1979-180 (Box 63, Folder 1010)
  Drawn by: Henderson Associates, Architecture and Interior Design, 1503 Colley Ave., Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Robert Henderson
- Alterations and Additions to Warehouse - Permit Number: 69279, Address: 326-328 S. Military Hwy., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-044 (Box 63, Folder 1011)
  Drawn by: Robbie F. Nurnberger, Architect and Planner, 601 Whitechapel Dr., Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: Mike A. Cobb; Commissioned by: Herbert Rockafeller
- [Single Family Residence] - Permit Number: 69474, Address: 1206 Elk Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-061 (Box 63, Folder 1012)
- Addition to Hood Chapel, African Methodist Episcopal Zion Church - Permit Number: 72589, Address: 611 Rockingham St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-337 (Box 63, Folder 1013)
  Drawn by: J. B. Cyrus, Certified Professional Engineer; Commissioned by: African Methodist Episocal Zion Church
- Remodeling for Spartan Market and Diner - Permit Number: 69347, Address: 3026 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-054 (Box 63, Folder 1014)
  Drawn by: Walsh, Ashe and Dills, A.I.A., Architects, Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: T. E. Morgan and Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: T. E. Morgan
- One Story, Two Bedroom Duplex - Permit Number: 72707, Address: 6342 Alexander St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-343 (Box 63, Folder 1015)
  Drawn by: H. R. Schippell, Certified Professional Engineer, 3232 Verdun Ave, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Man-Joe Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Socrates Manuel
- Renovation and Addition, 1308 Upper Brandon Place - Permit Number: 69292, Address: 1308 Upper Brandon Pl., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-048 (Box 63, Folder 1016)
  Drawn by: Robert L. Yoder, Architect, 828 Greensboro Ave., Virginia Beach, VA; Commissioned by: Myron Glassman
- Six Unit Apartment - Permit Number: 72568, Address: 9567 16th Bay St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-334 (Box 63, Folder 1017)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: William Hodges
- One Story, Two Bedroom Duplex - Permit Number: 69536, Address: 118 Forrest Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-070 (Box 63, Folder 1018)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Socrates E. Manuel; Commissioned by: Thomas Clark
- [Single Family Residence] - Permit Number: 70818, Address: 514 Berkley Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-157 (Box 63, Folder 1019)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: C and W Associates
- [Single Family Residence] - Permit Number: 73026, Address: 2941 Lens Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-364 (Box 63, Folder 1020)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: John A. Turner
- Plan "B", Four Bedroom Ranch - Permit Number: 72960, Address: 530 Louisa St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-356 (Box 63, Folder 1021)
- Addition to Mitch's Auto Service - Permit Number: 69476, Address: 2801 Lafayette Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-062 (Box 63, Folder 1022)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Schriver Construction; Commissioned by: Mitch's Auto Service
- [Addition and Alterations to Residence] - Permit Number: 65582, Address: 1031 Willingham St., 1979, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1979-187 (Box 63, Folder 1023)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Margaret E. Joyner
- Four Bedroom Ranch - Permit Number: 69522, Address: 2808 Keller Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-067 (Box 63, Folder 1024)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Shorebay Builders
- [Single Family Residence] - Permit Number: 72544, Address: 982 Teal Ct., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1980-332 (Box 63, Folder 1025)
  Drawn by: Cardinal Homes Incorporated, Wylliesburg, VA; Contractor: B and B Enterprises, Inc.; Commissioned by: Master Craft, Inc.
- [Roof Sign] - Permit Number: 69452, Address: 3200 Lafayette Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-060 (Box 64, Folder 1026)
  Drawn by: American Sign and Advertising Services, Inc.; Commissioned by: Powell McClellan Lumber Co.
- Chick-fil-A of Military Circle - Permit Number: 71660, Address: 30 Military Cir., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 19; Tag Number: 1980-213 (Box 64, Folder 1027)
  Drawn by: Cavender Associates, Architects, Jack E. Cavender, A.I.A., 1677 Dorsey Ave., East Point, GA; Contractor: C. F. Hardy Building Corp.; Commissioned by: Chick-fil-A
- [Addition to Residence] - Permit Number: 72952, Address: 1072 Johnstons Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-355 (Box 64, Folder 1028)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Floyd E. Sweats
- [Single Family Residence] - Permit Number: 71633, Address: 315 Cherry St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-207 (Box 64, Folder 1029)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Shorebay Builders, Inc.
- [Additions and Alterations to Residence] - Permit Number: 69293, Address: 912 Anna St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-049 (Box 64, Folder 1030)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Richard W. Tynes
- Proposed 4 Unit Apartment - Permit Number: 69401, Address: 9644 E. Ocean View Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-056 (Box 64, Folder 1031)
  Drawn by: E. N. Jasper, Developer; Commissioned by: E. N. Jasper
- 8 Unit Apartment Building - Permit Number: 72034, Address: 9606 18th Bay St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-301 (Box 64, Folder 1032)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: A. L. McGowan
- Addition and Alterations to St. Thomas A. M. E. Zion Church - Permit Number: 74135, Address: 1700 Melon St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 16; Tag Number: 1980-449 (Box 64, Folder 1033)
  Drawn by: Walsh, Ashe and Dills, A.I.A., Architects, Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: St. Thomas A. M. E. Zion Church
- O'Keefe Residence Addition - Permit Number: 70424, Address: 1033 Baldwin Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-132 (Box 64, Folder 1034)
  Drawn by: Hanbury and Company, P.C., Architecture and Interior Design, 204 Monticello Arcade, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: C and J Home Repairs, Inc.; Commissioned by: Joan J. O'Keefe, III
- One Family Residence for Mr. and Mrs. Manuel - Permit Number: 70056, Address: 7707 Leafwood Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-105 (Box 64, Folder 1035)
- The Kings Landing, A Restaurant Facility for Mr. David Cashvan - Permit Number: 74141, Address: 507 Front St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-451 (Box 64, Folder 1036)
  Drawn by: C. Richard Shepherd, Architect, 349-C4 Bute St., Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: The King's Landing (David Cashvan)
- Triplex [Three Family Apartment] - Permit Number: 74080, Address: 1268 W. Ocean View Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-439 (Box 64, Folder 1037)
  Drawn by: W. F. T.; Commissioned by: W. F. Thornton, Jr.
- New Development on Llewellyn Mews [9 Townhouses] - Permit Number: 74351-74359, Address: 300, 304, 308, 312, 316, 320, 324, 328, 332 Shirley Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1980-462 (Box 64, Folder 1038)
  Drawn by: Oliver, Smith and Cook, Ltd., Architects-Planners, Norfolk and Virginia Beach, VA; Commissioned by: S and G Corp.; Notes: Cost is $50,000 for each townhome.
- Office Addition, Capes Shipping Agencies, Inc. - Permit Number: 70342, Address: 1128 W. Olney Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 11; Tag Number: 1980-126 (Box 64, Folder 1039)
  Drawn by: McElroy and Baldwin, Architects, 1600 East Little Creek Rd., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Beach Buildings Corp.; Commissioned by: Capes Shipping Agencies, Inc.
- Garage - Permit Number: 70152, Address: 1830 Lightwood Ln., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-111 (Box 64, Folder 1040)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Jack E. Lee
- Addition to the Watts Residence - Permit Number: 70096, Address: 7334 Major Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-108 (Box 64, Folder 1041)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Michael J. Watts
- [Conversion of Residence into Office] - Permit Number: 70502, Address: 7428 Tidewater Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-136 (Box 64, Folder 1042)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: North Landing Line Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Dr. H. F. Pavon
- Sav-A-Ton, Inc., Pumper Development - Permit Number: 70098-70101, Address: 3350 Chesapeake Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-109 (Box 64, Folder 1043)
  Drawn by: McGee Corporation; Contractor: A. C. Clark Co.; Commissioned by: Sav-A-Ton, Inc.; Notes: Includes copy of Norfolk City Ordinance 26,180.
- McDonald's [Remodel] - Permit Number: 74416, Address: 8300 Hampton Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 13; Tag Number: 1980-446 (Box 64, Folder 1044)
  Drawn by: Harold O. Warner and Associates, Architects, Suite 201, 124 S. Lynnhaven Rd., Virginia Beach, VA; Commissioned by: McDonald's Corp.
- One Story, Two Bedroom Duplex - Permit Number: 70051, Address: 1264 W. 42nd St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-103 (Box 64, Folder 1045)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Bluestone Corp.
- [Alterations and Additions to] Exxon Motor Fuel Store - Permit Number: 74394-74399, Address: 132 Kempsville Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1980-466 (Box 64, Folder 1046)
  Drawn by: Exxon Company, U. S. A., A Division of Exxon Corporation, Marketing Department, Distribution and Engineering; Commissioned by: Exxon Corp.
- Proposed Addition to Tubb's Auto Parts - Permit Number: 74339, Address: 2215 Indian River Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-460 (Box 64, Folder 1047)
  Drawn by: Edwin B. Small, Architect-Engineer; Commissioned by: Tubbs Used Auto Parts
- Building Addition - Permit Number: 70334, Address: 7919 Halprin Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-122 (Box 64, Folder 1048)
  Drawn by: K. Y. Thrift, Civil Engineer; Commissioned by: H. L. Barnes
- House Plans for Stephen Dobson - Permit Number: 70161, Address: 6281 Wailes Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-112 (Box 64, Folder 1049)
  Drawn by: H. R. Schippell, Certified Professional Engineer, 3232 Verdun Ave, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Stephen Dobson
- One Story, Two Bedroom Duplex - Permit Number: 70050, Address: 1272 W. 42nd St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-104 (Box 64, Folder 1050)
- New Development on Llewellyn Mews - Permit Number: 70065-70076, Address: 320, 332, 340, 348, 1014, 1015, 1018, 1019, 1022, 1023, 1026, 1027 Llewellyn Mews, 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 15; Tag Number: 1980-107 (Box 65, Folder 1051)
  Drawn by: Oliver, Smith and Cook, Ltd., Architects-Planners, Norfolk and Virginia Beach, VA; Commissioned by: S and C Corp.; Notes: Single family residence @ $40,000 each.
- Norfolk Shipbuilding and Drydock Corp., Toilet and Locker Room Facility, Brambleton Plant - Permit Number: 74086, Address: 1915 Clairborne Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-441 (Box 65, Folder 1052)
  Drawn by: Gresham Metal Buildings Co., Inc., 1060 W. 26th St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Corp.
- Repairs to V. N. B. Parking Garage - Permit Number: 74085, Address: 130 Bank St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-440 (Box 65, Folder 1053)
  Drawn by: Abiouness, Cross, and Bradshaw, Inc., Consulting Structural Engineers, 4505 Colley Ave., Norfolk, VA, 3136 Zebulon Rd., Rocky Mount, NC; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Virginia National Bank
- United Virginia Bank, 12th Floor, Charles Nusbaum - Permit Number: 70310, Address: 5 Main Street Plaza East, 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-119 (Box 65, Folder 1054)
- [Alterations to 6 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 70500, Address: 1400 Colonial Ave., 1980, Media: Daizo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1980-135 (Box 65, Folder 1055)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Richard Matthews
- [Remodeling] First Calvary Baptist Church - Permit Number: 70464, Address: 813 Henry St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-134 (Box 65, Folder 1056)
  Drawn by: Elbert V. Walker, Certified Architect; Jose Francisco Soria, Architect, 4505 Colley Ave., Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: First Cavalry Baptist Church
- Alteration to Econo-Travel Motel - Permit Number: 74342, Address: 1050 Tidewater Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-461 (Box 65, Folder 1057)
  Drawn by: Leavitt Associates, Architects and Engineers, 4400 Colley Ave., Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Econo-Travel Motel
- Alterations to the Terrace Theater - Permit Number: 70341, Address: 7550 Tidewater Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-125 (Box 65, Folder 1058)
  Drawn by: Brookbank, Murphy, and Shields, Architects, Planners, Interior Designers, Columbus, GA; Contractor: Conrad Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: Plitt Southern Theaters
- Medical Center Hospital [Alterations] - Permit Number: 74104, Address: 3618 W. 37th St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-445 (Box 65, Folder 1059)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Thomas Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Medical Center Hospital
- Alterations to the Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Thomas D. Blanchard, Jr. - Permit Number: 70348, Address: 6213 Sylvan St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-127 (Box 65, Folder 1060)
  Drawn by: Yates and Berkeley Associates, Ltd., Architects, Planners, Interior Designers, 330 County St., Portsmouth, VA; Commissioned by: Thomas D. Blanchard
- Alterations to the Gautier Residence - Permit Number: 70063, Address: 417 Mayflower Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-106 (Box 65, Folder 1061)
  Drawn by: Rancorn Wildman Krause, A.I.A., Architects Planners, 2101 Executive Dr., Hampton, VA; Contractor: Smyth Construction Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: William Gautier
- Model "C" 3 Bedroom Ranch - Permit Number: 70281, 70282, Address: 982, 986 Avenue H, 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-116 (Box 65, Folder 1062)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Sifen Development
- Moores Store, A Division of Evans Products - Permit Number: 74370, 74371, Address: 956 E. Little Creek Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1980-464 (Box 65, Folder 1063)
  Drawn by: Walker S. Burdette; Commissioned by: Moores Store
- United Virginia Bank, 12th Floor, James C. Atkins - Permit Number: 70311, Address: 5 Main Plaza East, 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-118 (Box 65, Folder 1064)
- Alterations and Additions to 9660 E. Ocean View Ave., Circle Six Corporation - Permit Number: 74268, Address: 9660 Shore Dr. [E. Ocean View Ave.], 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-458 (Box 65, Folder 1065)
  Drawn by: Frank Carey Holton, Jr., A.I.A., Architect, 5500B Tidewater Dr., Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Charles Bashara
- Weather Enclosure for Outside Stairway- Telephone Center, Norfolk General Hospital Division of Medical Center Hospitals - Permit Number: 74287, Address: 600 Gresham Dr., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-459 (Box 65, Folder 1066)
  Drawn by: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc., 1038 W. 26th St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Norfolk General Hospital Division of Medical Center Hospitals
- Captain D's - Permit Number: 70324, 70325, Address: 831 E. Little Creek Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 23; Tag Number: 1980-121 (Box 65, Folder 1067)
  Drawn by: Stephen L. Cooper, Architect; Shoney's, Inc., 1727 Elm Hill, Nashville, TN; Contractor: Barr Construction Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Captain D's
- Second Floor West Wing Addition to the Administration Building for Norshipco Located at the Foot of Liberty Street, Berkeley Plant - Permit Number: 70043, Address: Foot of W. Liberty St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-102 (Box 65, Folder 1068)
  Drawn by:; Contractor: A. W. Tuttle and Son, Inc.; Commissioned by: Norshipco
- Tinee Giant, Remodeling of Sun Oil Service Station - Permit Number: 74127, Address: 4002 Granby St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-448 (Box 65, Folder 1069)
  Drawn by: Spigel, Herman, Chapman, Architects and Engineers, 420 W. Bute St., Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Rosso and Mostracco, Inc.
- Remodeling for Spartan Diner - Permit Number: 70247, Address: 3020 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-115 (Box 65, Folder 1070)
- Used Car Office and Repair Shop for Lou Colinsky, Jr. - Permit Number: 70213, Address: 881 E. Little Creek Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-114 (Box 65, Folder 1071)
  Drawn by: H. R. Schippell, Certified Professional Engineer, 3232 Verdun Ave, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: S. E. Manuel; Commissioned by: Lou Colinsky, Jr.
- Ghent Square Townhouses - Permit Number: 74363-74368, Address: 345, 349, 353, 357, 361, 365 W. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-463 (Box 65, Folder 1072)
  Drawn by: Verebely and Associates, Chesapeake, VA; Contractor: George Jensen, Inc.; Commissioned by: J. C. J. Corp.
- Ghent Commons - Permit Number: 74118-74121, Address: 226, 234, 242, 1409 Queens Way, 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 36; Tag Number: 1980-447 (Box 66, Folder 1073)
  Drawn by: Cohen and Haft, Koltz Kerxton, Associates, Architects and Planners; Commissioned by: Christopher Development Co.
- [Restaurant Alterations] - Permit Number: 74092, Address: 3134 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-443 (Box 66, Folder 1074)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: James Egglezos
- [1 Family Residence] - Permit Number: 70337, Address: 9254 First View St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1980-124 (Box 66, Folder 1075)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Harriet W. Dixon
- [Roof Signs] - Permit Number: 74140, Address: 8110 Hampton Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-450 (Box 66, Folder 1076)
  Drawn by: Lothorp, Neon and Plastic, 506 Pegram Dr., Tupelo, MS; Commissioned by: Henry Dodge
- [1 Family Residence with Garage] - Permit Number: 70381, Address: 1724 LaSalle Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-130 (Box 66, Folder 1077)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: James R. Gray
- [1 1/2 Car Garage] - Permit Number: 70350, Address: 1312 Maplewood Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-128 (Box 66, Folder 1078)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Ruby G. Gross
- Addition to Disabled American Veterans Chapter # 4 Home - Permit Number: 70450, Address: 2428 Ingleside Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-133 (Box 66, Folder 1079)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Lawder Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Disabled American Veterans Chapter #4
- Second and Attic Floor Alterations to 5656 Shenandoah Ave. for Mr. and Mrs. David Steadman - Permit Number: 74202, Address: 5656 Shenandoah Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-454 (Box 66, Folder 1080)
  Drawn by: A. W. Tuttle and Son, Inc., General Contractors, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: A. W. Tuttle and Son, Inc.; Commissioned by: Mr. and Mrs. David Steadman
- Two Story Apartment - Permit Number: 74093, Address: 453 E. Ocean View Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-442 (Box 66, Folder 1081)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Oceanside Builders, Inc.
- A Duplex Project for Calvin Miller - Permit Number: 74098, 74099, Address: 1437, 1441 W. 39th St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-444 (Box 66, Folder 1082)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Calvin Miller
- [1 Family Residence with Garage] - Permit Number: 60209, Address: 817 Fauquier St., 1978, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1978-108 (Box 66, Folder 1083)
- Three Bedroom Model B [Residence] - Permit Number: 74209, 74210, Address: 2505, 2513 Minnesota Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-455 (Box 66, Folder 1084)
  Drawn by: Helfant Bros., Inc.; Commissioned by: Helfant Bros., Inc.
- One Family Dwelling, Model B - Permit Number: 74385, Address: 419 Connecticut Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-465 (Box 66, Folder 1085)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Charles R. Johnson
- [Ten Unit, Two Story Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 74257, Address: 1644 Little Creek Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1980-457 (Box 66, Folder 1086)
  Drawn by: Kingsberry Homes, Boise Cascade Corporation; Commissioned by: Beam Development Corp.
- Proposed Office Space for Tidewater Towing - Permit Number: 74196, Address: 1195 Lance Rd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1980-453 (Box 66, Folder 1087)
  Drawn by: M. L. Walker; Commissioned by: W. J. Summers
- Three Bedroom Model A [Residence] - Permit Number: 74207, 74208, Address: 2525 Minnesota Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-456 (Box 66, Folder 1088)
- [Alteration to] Store Building for Colonial Stores, Inc. - Permit Number: 74046, Address: 8506 Chesapeake Blvd., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-436 (Box 66, Folder 1089)
  Drawn by: William G. Bursnall, Architect, Colonial Stores Incorporated, 2251 N. Sylvan Rd., East Point, GA; Contractor: J. E. Weddle and Assoc., Inc.; Commissioned by: Colonial Stores, Inc.
- [Alterations to] Intermission Restaurant - Permit Number: 74182, Address: 1501 Colley Ave., 1980, Media: Electrostatic prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-452 (Box 66, Folder 1090)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Metropolitan Home Maintenance; Commissioned by: Intermission Restaurant
- Four Bedroom Ranch - Permit Number: 74077, Address: 2722 Keller Ave., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-438 (Box 66, Folder 1091)
  Drawn by: Shorebay Builders; Commissioned by: Shorebay Builders
- [Addition to 1 Family Residence] - Permit Number: 70549, Address: 2635 Somme Ave., 1980, Media: Uknown; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1980-137 (Box 66, Folder 1092)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Richard L. Brown
- Addition and Alteration to Residence for Mr. and Mrs. Don Smith - Permit Number: 70322, Address: 2115 Hollybriar Pt., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-120 (Box 66, Folder 1093)
  Drawn by: McClurg and Wall, Architects,1559 Laskin Rd., Virginia Beach, VA; Contractor: Arthur-Knight Contracting Co.; Commissioned by: Don Smith
- [Two Family Residence] - Permit Number: 70026, Address: 811 W. 51st St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1980-101 (Box 66, Folder 1094)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Norman K. Tuttle, Jr.
- Three Bedroom Ranch - Permit Number: 70335, Address: 318 E. Chester St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1980-123 (Box 66, Folder 1095)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: William H. Hodges
- Proposed 4 Unit Apartment Building - Permit Number: 70106, Address: 9517 5th Bay St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1980-110 (Box 66, Folder 1096)
- Virginia National Bank Parking Garage Improvements - Permit Number: 70370, Address: 130 Bank St., 1980, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1980-129 (Box 66, Folder 1097)